As always.
いつものようにね
As usual?
いつものように?
It feels like being at home.
いつもの家でいる感じにさ
Do you always take your clothes off like that?
いつもそうやって脱ぐの?
It's tough, you know.
大変だよ、それね
What should I do?
どうしよう
No, I like the style.
いや、スタイルいいなぁ
Are you going to take off your socks?
これさ、靴下を脱ぐの?
Shall I take it off?
脱いちゃおうか
As expected, it would be amazing if you could enter it as it is.
さすがにそれさ、入ったまま入ったらすごいよね
I mean, I said I keep wearing them all the time.
だって、ずっと履きっぱなしで言ったじゃん
nice.
いいね
I prefer to keep them on all the time, but
ずっと履きっぱなしがいいんだけど、
As expected, taking a bath is dangerous.
さすがの風呂はしてやばい
Wow, you're taking off your underwear and two glasses at the same time.
すげぇ、パンツと2杯緒に脱ぐんだね
Shall we go?
行っちゃおうか
So, you don't tie your hair?
あれ、髪結ばないの?
Was it warm?
あったか
Can't get in?
入らない?
Enter, enter.
入る、入る
why?
なんで?
Is that better?
そのほうがいい?
She's a maiden.
乙女だね
He's a fun guy.
楽しがり屋だね
I'll put some water down there.
下に水入れてくるね
Max to max.
マックスまでマックス
Isn't there Max?
マックスないのか?
Max.
マックス
It's funny when we go together.
二人で行くの笑うのね
What are your hobbies?
趣味は?
What, a hobby?
何、趣味?
I don't have any hobbies.
趣味ないよ
What do you mean?
何のこと?
Are you at home?
家にいる?
I'm at home.
家 にいる
You don't know?
お前、知らない?
i don't know.
知らない
I'm coming.
来るぞ
What kind?
どんなの?
I'll show you.
見せるのね
Are you home when you go?
行くときに帰っているの?
I won't go.
行かない
Do you get sleepy if you don't touch me?
触らないと眠くなるの?
It will be.
なる
Women sleep to sleep.
女性は寝るために寝るの
I can sleep.
寝れる
why?
なんで?
Men don't have that.
男にはそれないんだけど
Men sleep too.
男も寝るじゃん
I'm going to sleep though.
寝るけど
There's nothing left to do soon.
一体は後はすぐにない
Wow, isn't it lukewarm?
すごい、ぬるくない?
Because we have verification time.
検証タイムがあるから
After about 30 minutes, I was in a state of mind.
30分くらいちょっとね、方針状態になる
I want to do magic.
魔法したくなってます
It's different though.
どちらか違うんだけど
It's getting lukewarm.
ぬるくなってます
What is your favorite purchase?
好きな買い物は?
meat.
肉
Do you like meat?
肉好きなの?
There's meat on it.
肉がかかっている
Like this.
こうやって
I'm taking pictures.
撮っているじゃん
Are you taking pictures?
撮っている?
I'm taking pictures.
撮っているよ
It's a big deal when it comes to your state of mind.
心境だと大きいよね
It's in my hair.
髪の毛の中がある
There isn't.
ないよ
Looks like a bigger.
バイガーみたいだね
At Hanakawa.
花川で
No, I'm not defending you anymore.
いや、もう弁護してないわ
I really like it though.
俺めっちゃ好きなんだけど
It's in your hair.
髪の毛の中があるじゃん
picture?
え?
It's hair though.
髪の毛なんだけど
Is it cute?
可愛いのかな?
It's not cute.
可愛くない
A face flashed.
ひらめみた顔が
This is the face.
この顔です
And it happens to me too.
それと俺も起こる
I happen.
俺が起こる
It's not cute.
可愛くない
It's quite popular.
結構人気だよ
Well then, go up.
じゃあ、上がれ
It's completely gone now, hasn't it?
まったくなったでしょ
Flow?
流す?
Something I always do.
いつもやるやつ
I'm coming.
行ってくるね
It's really warm.
なんかめっちゃ暖かい
Really.
ほんまに
Next time I'll do the trick.
次はチンチン流すやつか
I feel like I can always flow.
いつも流せる感じに
want?
欲しい?
Ching Chin.
チンチン
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
feet.
足
I put it away and haven't taken it out yet.
しまって、まだ抜いてない
I'll go.
行くよ
Nektoku is difficult.
ネクトクはむずいんだよ
yes.
はい
It's been about two years.
2年ぶりくらいだね
How have you been?
元気だった?
I wanted to meet you.
会いたかったんだよね
I've always wanted to meet you.
ずっと会いたかった
Do you like sex?
エッチ好き?
I like sex.
エッチ好き
It's the same as always.
相変わらずだね
nice.
いいね
Sex two years ago was really good.
2年前のセックスは すごく良かったな
You don't remember, do you?
覚えてないでしょ
Look here.
こ っち見て
I like it, it's cute.
いいね、かわいいね
Look here.
こっち見てよ
I said let's have sex.
エッチしようって言ったね
Let's have sex.
エッチしよう
Hello.
こんにちは
It's raining.
雨ですね
It was really humid.
湿気やばかったね
Was it humid?
湿気やばかった?
It was extremely humid.
湿気やばかった
It's raining.
雨だね
How do you feel on a rainy day?
雨の日ってどんな気分になる?
bothersome.
めんどくさい
bothersome?
めんどくさい?
It's been a while since we met.
久しぶりだね、会うのね
How many years has it been since?
何年ぶりくらいですか?
It's been about two years.
2年ぶりくらいだね
How have you been?
元気だった?
fine.
元気
I really wanted to meet you.
会いたかったんだよね、俺は本当に
I've always wanted to meet you.
ずっと会いたかった
I wanted to meet you and was wondering when we could meet.
会いたくて、いつ会えるのかなと思ってさ
It's far from where I live.
住んでるところは遠いじゃん
That's why we hadn't been able to meet for a long time, but now we're finally able to meet.
だから、なかなか会えなかったんだけど やっと会えたってことで
hey.
ね
Ah, it's still cute.
あ いかわらず可愛いですね
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いね
nice.
いいね
Are you still naughty?
あいかわらずエッチなの?
I don't know.
わかんない
Do you like sex?
エッチ好き?
like.
好き
It's the same as always.
あいかわらずだね
nice.
いいね
Sex two years ago was amazing.
2年前のセックスは すげえ良かったな
You don't remember, do you?
覚えてないでしょ
I remember, I remember.
覚えてる覚えてる
I remember it at all.
全然覚えてるよ
It was really intense at that time.
あの時すげえだって激しかったもん
Have you had a child?
子供できちゃった?
I let it cum inside me.
俺 の中に出しちゃったけど
Did you make it?
できたの?
That's a lie, right?
嘘でしょ
It hasn't been done yet.
できてないよね
Even I let it out until it reached the CPU.
俺でも中にCPUに届くまで出しちゃったからね
I can see your pants.
パンツ見えてる
That's amazing.
すげえ良いな
wide.
広い
Can you see it?
見えてる?
I can see it, I can see it.
見えてる見えてる
Suddenly pants.
いきなりパンツ
I'm wearing it.
つけてるね
Don't put it on.
つけてな
Not wearing hair?
毛つけてない?
You're wearing hair.
毛つけてるじゃん
I'm wearing it.
つ けてるよ
nice.
いいね
This makes a great picture.
これすごい絵になる
It'll be a picture.
絵になるよ
It makes a great picture.
すごい絵になる
What are you doing?
何やってるの?
I just play games.
ゲームばっかやってるんだもん
Game geek?
ゲームオタク?
It's a game.
ゲームだもんね
Really nice style.
ホントスタイルいいよね
I gained weight.
太った
I'm not fat.
太ってないよ
It won't change much.
あんま変わんないじゃん
Then hold it horizontally.
じゃあ横くるって持って
It won't change at all.
全然変わんないじゃん
nice.
いいね
Let's take a look from below.
下から見ちゃおう
I feel like I'm getting far away.
遠ざかってしてる感じ
From below this.
この下から
I feel like I'm getting far away.
遠 ざかってしてる感じ
Open it.
開いて
scared?
怖い?
It's kind of warm.
なんか暖かいね
warm.
暖かい
Isn't it warm?
暖かくない?
warm.
暖かい
Is it closed?
閉めてる?
Isn't it closed?
閉めてない?
It's closed.
閉めてるね
nice.
いいね
Shall we sit down then?
じゃあ座っちゃおうか
It's cute.
かわいいね
When was the last time you had sex?
最近いつセックスしたの?
When was your first experience?
初めての経験いつ?
17?
Where did you do it?
どこでやったの?
Really?
ホントに?
Seriously?
マジか
It's normal.
普通だね
Didn't you do it outside?
外でやらなかったの?
It's outside.
外だね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Look here.
こっち見て
nice.
いいね
It's cute.
かわいいね
Look at me.
見つめてよ
Did I say let's have sex?
エッチしようって言った?
Let's have sex.
エッチしよう
nice.
いいね
It's cute.
かわいいね
Is it okay to bully you?
いじめていっていい?
As usual?
いつものように?
Can I do it?
やっていい?
Like before?
前みたいに?
Can I do it like before?
前みたいにやっていい?
Soft, as always.
やわらかいね、相変わらず
Are they connected?
繋がってるのか?
one piece.
ワンピース
Long hair.
髪長い
Can you feel my breasts?
おっぱい感じる?
It's so soft.
すげえやわらかい
My boobs came out.
おっぱい出てきた
I was a little excited though.
ちょっと興奮したけど
It's up.
アップだよ
close.
近い
Her breasts are up.
おっぱいアップだよ
look?
見る?
No.
いやだ
What does it look like?
どんな感じに映ってるか
You can see it, right?
見えるでしょ?
It feels like this.
こう いう感じ
copper?
どう?
No way.
やだ
Do you see your breasts rising?
自分のおっぱい上がって見えてる?
nice.
いいね
Just standing there.
ちっぽり立ってる
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいいの?
ど こが気持ちいいの?
close.
近い
Does it feel good there?
そ こ が気持ちいいの?
Boobs open engine.
おっぱいオープンエンジン
cold?
冷たい?
cold.
冷たい
It's hitting the range.
レンジに当たってるよ
That's good.
いいよね
Come here more.
もっとこっち来て
Sleep.
寝て
Can I sleep now?
今 寝てていい?
tight?
きつい?
It's tough, isn't it?
きついよね
Let's be a little slanted.
ちょっと斜めになろうか
Kindness.
優しめ
It's better to be stronger.
もっと強いほうがいい
Shall I pull it out?
抜いちゃおうか
Shall I take it all out?
全部抜いちゃう?
I pulled it out.
抜いちゃったね
Can I hit it?
当たっていい?
Will it be a hit?
当たっちゃう?
I want you to show me your anus too.
アナルも見せてほしい
That's the best.
それ最高
This is dangerous.
やばいこれ
Wow, that's awesome.
すげえ、パックリ
I can see the map.
マップ割り見えてる
Wow, the map is beautiful.
すげえ、マップ綺麗じゃん
Which is better?
どこがいい?
Look here.
こっち見て
Will it be a hit?
当たっちゃう?
Then open the map yourself.
じゃあマップ自分で開いて
often.
よく
Are you giving medical treatment?
診療してる?
Is it getting across?
伝わってる?
In your hand.
手に
terrible.
やばい
You're right.
上当たってる
where?
どこ?
Kuri-chan, you're right.
くりちゃん、上当たってる
That's terrible.
やばいわ
You're right.
上当たってる
It doesn't really hit me.
めっちゃ当たってない
That's terrible.
やばいわ
towards the hand.
手 に向けて
terrible.
やばい
Is this better?
こっちの方がいい?
Would you like something more dangerous?
もっとやばさがいい?
Open it properly.
ちゃんと開いてよ
With both hands.
両手で
Around here.
この辺
Look here.
こっち見て
Which way is it?
どっちになってるか
Push and push?
押し押してあんの?
Shall we go?
いっちゃう?
I'll make you feel more comfortable.
もっと気持ちいいやつにしてあげるよ
I'll do it with something that feels more comfortable.
も っと気持ちいいやつでやっちゃうよ
Are you sleeping well?
上 手 く寝てる?
You're sleeping well.
上手く寝てるじゃん
Look.
ほら
This is terrible.
これやばいよ
This is dangerous.
これやばいやつ
It makes me hungry.
お腹入っちゃうやつ
The one that goes into your stomach.
お腹の中入っちゃうやつ
Do it.
やってな
I'm going to proceed here.
こっちで進めるっていう
Look.
ほ ら
Lovely
ラブリーじゃ
yeah.
ん
Butt.
お 尻
In your stomach.
お腹の中で
You're sleeping well.
上手く寝てるじゃん
copper?
どう?
What's going on?
どうなってるの?
What will happen?
どうなるの?
this is?
これは?
hey?
ね?
Hey, right here.
ちょい、ここさ
this.
これ
A mess.
ぐちゃぐちゃ
terrible.
やばい
This is terrible.
やばいよ、これ
Look.
ほら
It's just a mess.
ぐちゃぐちゃだけ入ってる
Look.
ほ ら
This is so fast.
これで、めっちゃ早い
This way.
こっち
Come in here too and do it properly.
こっちも入って、ちゃんと
Come in here too.
こっちも入って
Let's go, what will happen?
いっちゃう、どうなるの?
What will happen?
どうなるの?
Come in.
入ってきて
Don't stop.
止めちゃダメだよ
It's all messed up.
ぐちゃぐちゃ入ってる
I'll come in.
入るよ
Awesome.
すげー
It's coming in.
入ってきてる
It's disgusting, it's disgusting.
ぐやらしいし、ぐやらしいし
what happened?
どうしたの?
This is terrible.
これ、やばいな
It's even more dangerous.
もっとやばいやつね
It's the one I was wondering about earlier.
さっき気になってたやつだよ
put in?
入れる?
This looks like a penis.
おちんちんみたいだよ、これ
What do you think?
どうでしょ?
I agree.
そうだね
I can come in though.
入っていれるんだけど
I'll do it.
やっちゃう
It's a bit of a mess, so I'll get into it right away.
なんかぐちゃぐちゃだから、すぐに入る
Look.
ほら
I'll do it.
やっちゃう
How far can it go?
どこまで入るの?
Do you want to enter?
あんま入んの?
this?
これ?
Are you holding it down?
押さえてる?
I'm going to take a shower, so please masturbate.
シャワー行くから、 オナにしてて
Something I always do.
いつもやるやつ
It's so light.
すげー軽くる
Awesome.
すげー
It's too rough, I'm trying to lighten it up.
あらすぎてるわ、軽くしてる
Awesome.
すげー
terrible.
やばい
I can't get out.
抜けない
After all, the skin on my hands didn't come off anymore.
やっぱり手肌が抜けなくなったんだよ
What should I do?
どうする?
I can't get out.
抜けない
Yay!
やったー
It's so warm.
あんま暖かい
It's really warm.
あんまめっちゃ暖かい
I can't escape.
抜 けない
I can't get out.
抜けない
I can't escape.
抜 けない
I can't get out.
抜けない
Well then, let's lick your dick next time.
じゃあ次はおちんちなめようか
I feel like I can always flow with it.
いつも流せる感じにね
I can't get out.
抜けない
I can't escape.
抜 けない
Should I cut it?
切っていこうかな
Let's cut it.
切っていこう
It has decreased tremendously.
すげー減った
Does Chin-chan feel good?
ちんちゃん気持ちいい?
It's in.
入ってるよ
Please let me sleep.
寝きさせてください
Just lower it.
あんま下げる
here?
ここ?
Is it difficult?
むずい?
It's difficult.
むずい
My legs are really stiff right now.
めっちゃ足つってる今
It's so amazing.
めっちゃすかいさ
Did you go?
いった?
It's gone, I haven't taken it out yet.
しまった、まだ抜いてない
I'll pull it out.
抜くよ
It's really hard.
めっちゃくちゃむずいんだよ
Good.
よいしょ
Oh, it came out, it came out.
おー、出てきた出てきた
Oh, dripping dripping.
あー、垂れた垂れた
It's dripping.
垂れてきたよ
Show me your face.
ちょっと顔見せて
Kamanko.
かまんこ
Inside I went.
いっちゃった中に
Maybe I'll have a child, maybe I'll have a child.
子供、子供できたたぶん
What should I do?
どうする?
I had a child.
子供できちゃった
Aren't I sweaty?
俺汗やばくない?
Are you writing?
書いてる?
Isn't it written down?
書いてなくね?
What is it?
何だよ
What? I haven't written it.
何だよ、書いてない
It came out.
出た
It came out great.
すげー出てきた
That's terrible.
やばいね
how was it?
どうだった?
Your anus is huge.
アナルでかいな
It's a lie, it's a lie.
嘘だ、嘘だ
I'll put my finger in.
指入るよ
How was it over there?
あっちどうでした?
how was it?
どうだった?
It was interesting.
おもしろかった
Lastly, just clean the tip.
最後、先っこだけお掃除してよ
Last of cleaning.
お掃除のラスト
Like Rena Tanaka.
田中玲奈みたいに
Rena Tanaka is shining the light on me.
田中玲奈ちゃんが 照らしてくれてる
Aren't you happy?
嬉 しくないの?
I think it's super cute, but...
超可愛いと思うんだけど、俺は
What will you do?
どんなにする?
sour.
酸っぱい
That's a very realistic feeling.
すげーリアルな感想だね
It's all my sweat that's dripping down here.
ここまで垂れてるやつ 全部俺の汗だね
Lastly, please give us your thoughts.
最後、感想お願いします
What do you think?
何感想?
how was it?
どうだった?
Try it.
やってみて
It's hot because I'm wearing a mask.
マスクしてるから熱い
Let me know your thoughts.
ちょっと感想聞かせてよ
Will we do it again?
またやる?
Let's cosplay, next time.
コスプレしよう、今度
Have you ever done it?
や ったことある?
Safe is good.
セーフがいい
But even if that were the case, it would be no good if you took it off from the beginning.
でもその仮に最初から脱いじゃダメ
Until the end.
最後まで
All the way to the end?
最後もずっと?
Let's do that.
やろうよ、それ
Shall we do it?
やっちゃう?
Well then, someone who will look at me,
じゃあなんかさ、 見てくれる人、
I think you say that.
言うと思うんだよ
This is my last word.
これをね、 一言最後
Quite a few words.
だいぶ一言
Look at my guy.
私のやつを見てください
After all, this is going to be a work of art.
一応これは作品になるわけだからさ
With myself.
自分とね
Me and us?
自分と俺らのか
So, there's something about that.
それでなんか、 それに対してなんか
Please watch a lot.
たくさん見てください
Can I do the same as this?
これと同じにしていいの?
Please make it the same.
いっぱい同じにしてください
So let's believe in something again next time.
じゃあ次もまた あることを信じよう
Well then, cosplay.
じゃあコスプレね
Well then, thank you for your hard work.
じゃあお疲れ様
bye bye.
バイ バイ
Wave.
手振って
good night.
おやすみなさい
See you then.
じゃあね
bye bye.
バイバイ